http://infreethought.org/privacy-policy

Inland Northwest Freethought SocietySearch this site
NavigationWelcomeAbout UsResourcesOther OrganizationsLinksVideosConsider ReadingAnnouncementsMembershipServicesInland Northwest Freethought Achievement AwardContact UsBooks We OwnPrivacy PolicySitemap
Privacy Policy
This
Privacy Policy explains how the Inland Northwest Freethought Society
(INFS) collects and uses the personal information collected on its Web
sites. The following applies to the gathering and dissemination of
information through all resources hosted at  http://www.infreethought.org/   and may be changed by the INFS at any
time.
What We Collect
The INFS gathers the following types of information about users:
Contact Information:This information which is given voluntarily allows communications
such as emails, podcasts, and participation in
online advocacy campaigns.
Aggregated tracking information:The INFS analyzes visitor demographic and traffic statistics to
improve our web sites. Under no circumstances does the INFS divulge
such information  about an individual user to a third party.
Personal Data:The INFS stores all personal data voluntarily provided by Web site
visitors. The INFS does not share, sell, or provide this information to
third parties.
Cookies:We may provide a small data file called a "cookie" which is stored
on your computer. This is intended to enhance the browsing experience
of Web site visitors. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or
read cookie files created by other sites. Certain areas of the INFS Web
site utilize cookies to automatically store login information for
subsequent visits.  If you are using a public computer or prefer not to
receive cookies, you can alter the configuration of your browser to
reject cookies.
Questions
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices
of this Web site, or your dealings with this Web site, please direct
your questions                     by email to   webmaster@infreethought.org.   Please
reference this Privacy Policy in your subject line.
Sign in|Recent Site Activity|Report Abuse|Print Page|Powered By Google Sites
